Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997 UE.4.1.7
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals
1936-1997
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.7
15 Linear Feet (12 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 7 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Related Material
UE District 7 Records, 1960s-1990s, UE.15.7, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 758 Records, 1990s-2000s, UE.16.758, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 764 Records, 1980s-1990s, UE.16.764, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 765 Records, 1970s-1980s, UE.16.765, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 767 Records, 1960s-1990s, UE.16.767, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 777 Records, 1990s, UE.16.777, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 790 Records, 1990s, UE.16.790, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 791 Records, 1990s-2000s, UE.16.791, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 794 Records, 1990s, UE.16.794, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 798 Records, 1998-1999, UE.16.798, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 7 and District 7 Locals, 1936-1997, UE.4.1.7, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 7 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) consisted of locals throughout Ohio and are now part of the UE's Eastern Region. This series contains files on UE District 7 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 7. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Ohio -- History -- 20th century; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Ohio -- History; Labor; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 7; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; Emspak, Julius; Matles, James J.
- District 7, 1.
  - District 7 Officers Lists, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - District 7 Officers Resolutions, 1943-1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Release of Lederman, July 10-11, 1943; 1.
    - Discussion of United States Presidential Candidate, January 11, 1948; 2.
    - Reformation of Membership Rights, November 8, 1948; 3.
  - District 7 Officers Minutes, April 11, 1942-November 8, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District 7 Officers Minutes, December 20, 1948-July 21, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 7 Officers Minutes, September 9, 1951-June 14, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - District 7 Officers Minutes, July 18, 1953-August 5, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 7 Officers Minutes, 1976-1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - District 7 Constitution Correspondence, March 16-17, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - District 7 Membership Lists (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District 7 Membership Resolutions, January 11,1942-January 7, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - National Defense Production, January 11, 1942; 1.
    - War Production, January 11, 1942; 2.
    - Utility Workers, January 14, 1945; 3.
    - Wage Policy, July 10, 1948; 4.
    - Taft-Hartley, July 10, 1948; 5.
    - Organization, July 10, 1948; 6.
    - General Officers, July 10, 1948; 7.
    - UE News, July 11, 1948; 8.
    - Foreign Policy, July 11, 1948; 9.
    - Arthur Gaeth Program, July 11, 1948; 10.
    - Labor Unity, July 11, 1948; 11.
    - Presidential Election, July 11, 1948; 12.
    - Wage Freezes, January 7, 1950; 13.
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, December 13, 1936-June 6, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, July 11-September 19, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, January 10-July 27, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, October 11, 1942-April 2, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, July 9, 1944-March 20, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, July 10, 1948-January 8, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, February 14-April 9, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, July 16, 1949-September 9, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, October 14, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, January 12-July 19, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, October 25, 1952-July 18, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, October 17, 1953-July 10, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - District 7 Membership Minutes, Octobr 16, 1954-January 22, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - District 7 Ohio-Kentucky Council Meeting Minutes, April 18-December 17, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 7 Ohio-Kentucky Conference Board, October 8-December 17, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - District 7 Joint Wage Committee, January 13-March 31, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Joint Wage Committee Minutes, January 13, 1948; 1.
    - Robert Elsner to Friend with January 6, 1948, Press Release, January 22, 1948; 2.
    - Elsner to All Officers with Ticket; Health, Welfare and Security Proposals; Important Bulletin; January 6, 1948, Press Release; and Leaflet, January 22, 1948; 3.
    - Joint Wage Committee Minutes, January 27, 1948; 4.
    - Joint Wage Committee Minutes, March 3, 1948; 5.
    - Joint Wage Committee Minutes, March 23, 1948; 6.
    - Joint Wage Committee Minutes, March 31, 1948; 7.
  - District 7 Amalgamated Local Conference, February 18, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, March 9, 1944-February 3, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Janet Barish to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Check, March 9, 1944; 1.
    - Barish to Phyllis Webster Regarding Check, October 18, 1944; 2.
    - Barish to Victor Decavitch Regarding Insurance, October 25, 1944; 3.
    - Barish to Webster Regarding Check, October 25, 1944; 4.
    - Barish to Decavitch Regarding Expense Report, February 15, 1945; 5.
    - Barish to Florence Bunn Regarding Check, June 11, 1945; 6.
    - Barish to Ella Garner Regarding Check, June 25, 1945; 7.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Insurance, August 3, 1945; 8.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Salary, August 3, 1945; 9.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Check, September 17, 1945; 10.
    - Barish to Henry Fiering Regarding Check, October 15, 1945; 11.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Supplies, October 25, 1945; 12.
    - Barish to Decavitch Regarding Salary, November 21, 1945; 13.
    - Barish to Bunn Regarding Check, November 23, 1945; 14.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Salary, March 19, 1946; 15.
    - Barish to David Kanes Regarding Insurance, March 20, 1946; 16.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Check, March 25, 1946; 17.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Business, February 3, 1947; 18.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, April 30, 1947-April 3, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Janet Barish to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Insurance, April 30, 1947; 1.
    - Barish to June Kaplin Regarding Bill, August 20, 1947; 2.
    - Barish to Vejlupek Regarding Insurance, November 6, 1947; 3.
    - Barish to Lemuel Markland Regarding Check, February 3, 1948; 4.
    - Barish to Markland Regarding Check, Februrary 19, 948; 5.
    - Barish to Markland Regarding Check, March 5, 1948; 6.
    - Barish to Markland Regarding Supplies, July 21, 1948; 7.
    - Barish to Paula Fischer Regarding Insurance, September, 22, 1948; 8.
    - Barish to Fischer Regarding Check, October 11, 1949; 9.
    - Barish to Herb Hirschberg Regarding Per Capita Record, April 6, 1950; 10.
    - Barish to Hirschberg Regarding Per Capita, May 18, 1950; 11.
    - Barish to June Ezelle Regarding Insurance, October 11, 1950; 12.
    - Barish to Joseph Kres Regarding Business, January 10, 1951; 13.
    - Barish to Elizabeth Barrow Regarding Supplies, April 23, 1951; 14.
    - Barish to Kres Regarding Check, October 22, 1951; 15.
    - Barish to Sterling Neal Regarding Check, February 4, 1952; 16.
    - Barish to Elizabeth Burrows Regarding Statement, April 3, 1953; 17.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, April 28, 1937-October 20, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Janet Barish to David Fisher Regarding Check, April 15, 1952; 1.
    - Barish to O.C. Lantz Regarding Payment, January 6, 1953; 2.
    - Barish to Sterling Neal Regarding Bill, Octobe 18, 1954; 3.
    - Barish to Neal Regarding Bill, October 20, 1954; 4.
    - Walter Barry to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Union Organization, April 2, 1941; 5.
    - William Bentley Letter Regarding Election, April 3, 1942; 6.
    - Barry Bingham to Neal Regarding Court Hearing, November 3, 1953; 7.
    - E.G. Bunting to Walter Miller Regarding Committee Meeting, April 28, 1937; 8.
    - Bill Chan to Victor Decavitch Regarding Radio Script, November 26, 1945; 9.
    - Cahn to Vejlupek Regarding Publications, January 31, 1947; 10.
    - Cahn to Ruth Merson Regarding Literature Displays, April 1, 1947; 11.
    - Cahn to Vejlupek Regarding Publications, April 17, 1947; 12.
    - Cahn to Steve Rosner Regarding Appointment, May 19, 1947; 13.
    - Cahn to Lem Markland Regarding Publications, May 28, 1947; 14.
    - Cahn to Hyman Lumer Regarding Publications, June 20, 1947; 15.
    - Cahn to Lumer Regarding Supplies, July 6, 1947; 16.
    - Cahn to Vejlupek Regarding Publications, Decemer 5, 1947; 17.
    - Cahn to Markland Regarding Radio Broadcasts, December 8, 1947; 18.
    - Cahn to Lumer Regarding Publications, Decemer 15, 1947; 19.
    - Cahn to Lumer Regarding Publications, January 20, 1948; 20.
    - Cahn to Thomas Corner Regarding Publications, January 20, 1948; 21.
    - Cahn to Lumer Regarding Appointment, June 22, 1948; 22.
    - Cahn to Lumer Regarding Publications, December 14, 1948; 23.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, October 31, 1936-October 15, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Bill Cahn to Jake Staas Regarding Publications, January 4, 1949; 1.
    - Cahn to Hy Lumer Regarding Press, May 26, 1949; 2.
    - Cahn to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Radio Script, June 21, 1949; 3.
    - Cahn to Paula Fisher Regarding Publications, October 17, 1949; 4.
    - Cahn to Fisher Regarding Publications, October 18, 1949; 5.
    - Cahn to Sterling Neal Regarding Bill, October 15, 1954; 6.
    - Cahn to Ruth Merson Regarding Press Coverage, 7.
    - James Carey to Walter Miller Regarding Auto Workers, October 31, 1936; 8.
    - Carey to A.C. Bishop Regarding Publications, December 18, 1936; 9.
    - Carey to Bishop Regarding Public Relations, December 21, 1939; 10.
    - Carey to Walter Miller Regarding Local Charter, January 22, 1937; 11.
    - Carey to Miller Regarding Local Charter, February 24, 1937; 12.
    - Carey to John Keller Regarding Appointment, September 17, 1937; 13.
    - Carey to K. Kirkendall Regarding Locals Meeting, December 6, 1937; 14.
    - Carey to Kirkendall Regarding Delay in Correspondence, December 30, 1937; 15.
    - Carey to Kirkendall Regarding Locals Meeting, January 20, 1938; 16.
    - Carey to Kirkendall Regarding Council Meeting, February 9, 1938; 17.
    - Carey to Kirkendall Regarding Unemployment, April 28, 1938; 18.
    - Carey to Vejlupek Regarding Board Meeting, November 25, 1940; 19.
    - Carey to Vejlupek Regarding Board Meeting Proposal, December 5, 1940; 20.
    - Carey to Kirkendall Regarding Communism in Union, March 5, 1943; 21.
    - E. Connolly to UE Regarding Identity Inquiry, December 28, 1948; 22.
    - Joe Dermody to Victor Decavitch Regarding Post War Plant, January 7, 1945; 23.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, May 2, 1936-August 25, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - P. Dillon to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Strike Settlement, June 11, 1941; 1.
    - James Divine to Nat Spero Regarding Job List, April 21, 1949; 2.
    - K. Ellsworth to A. Bishop Regarding Publications, September 18, 1936; 3.
    - Julius Emspak to Walter Miller Regarding Locals Charter, May 2, 1936; 4.
    - Emspak to K. Kirkendall Regarding Local Meetings, May 11, 1936; 5.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Local Organization, May 16, 1936; 6.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Press, May 18, 1936; 7.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Press, June 17, 1936; 8.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding RCA Strike, July 20, 1936; 9.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Conference, August 4, 1936; 10.
    - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Charter, August 11, 1936; 11.
    - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Meeting, August 15, 1936; 12.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Chater, August 19, 1936; 13.
    - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Charter, September 14, 1936; 14.
    - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Meeting, September 19, 1936; 15.
    - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Credit Union, September 29, 1936; 16.
    - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Credit Union, October 6, 1936; 17.
    - Emspak to Bishop Regarding Check, November 11, 1936; 18.
    - Emspak to David Creps Regarding Local Organization, November 11, 1936; 19.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Local Meeting, November 24, 1936; 20.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Organizational Drive, December 8, 1936; 21.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Credentials, December 8, 1936; 22.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Meeting, December 1, 1936; 23.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Council Meeting, December 30, 1936; 24.
    - Emspak to Creps Regarding Local Business, February 25, 1937; 25.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Check, March 11, 1937; 26.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Credentials, May 25, 1937; 27.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Local Lists, May 26, 1937; 28.
    - Emspak to Arthur Garfield Regarding Press, July 19, 1937; 29.
    - Emspak to Charles Killinger Regarding Supplies, July 26, 1937; 30.
    - Emspak to Joseph Albert Regarding Cincinnati Situation, August 6, 1937; 31.
    - Emspak to Coleman Taylor Regarding Local Delegates, August 11, 1937; 32.
    - Emspak to Joseph Albert Regarding Crosley Plant, August 13, 1937; 33.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Charter Fee, August 13, 1937; 34.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Charter, August 21, 1937; 35.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Dues, August 23, 1937; 36.
    - Emspak to Miller Regarding Convention, August 25, 1937; 37.
    - Emspak to Albert Regarding Charter, August 25, 1937; 38.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, August 30, 1937-September 25, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Julius Esmpak to Tim McCormik Regarding Defiance Situation, August 30, 1937; 1.
    - Emspak to K. Kirkendall Regarding Check, September 13, 1937; 2.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Requisitions, September 13, 1937; 3.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Supplies, September 14, 1937; 4.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Charter, September 29, 1937; 5.
    - Emspak to August Scholle Regarding Charter, October 28, 1937; 6.
    - Emspak to E.M. Albright Regarding Circular Letter, November 4, 1937; 7.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Statement of Locals, November 6, 1937; 8.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Charter, November 10, 1937; 9.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Conference, November 15, 1937; 10.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Check, November 22, 1937; 11.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Check, November 26, 1937; 12.
    - Emspak to Albright Regarding Resolutions, December 3, 1937; 13.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Local Affiliation, December 23, 1937; 14.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Check, December 29, 1937; 15-16.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Amalgamation, January 14, 1938; 17.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Expense Report, January 31, 1938; 18.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Charter, February 11, 1938; 19.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Check, March 21, 1938; 20-21.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Check, April 4, 1938; 22.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Check, April 16, 1938; 23.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Election, April 30, 1938; 24.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Dues, June 1, 1938; 25.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Charter, July 28, 1938; 26.
    - Emspak to Kirkendall Regarding Letter of Reference, August 27, 1938; 27.
    - Emspak Letter Regarding Letter to Recommunications, August 27, 1938; 28.
    - Emspak to Victor Larid Regarding Mailing List, September 13, 1940; 29.
    - Emspak to Harry Harmon Regarding Mailing List, September 13, 1940; 30.
    - Emspak to Marvin Miniard Regarding Mailing List, September 13, 1940; 31-32.
    - Emspak to Otto Lommatzsch Regarding Bill, September 24, 1940; 33.
    - Emspak to George Rothleitner Regarding Debt, September 24, 1940; 34.
    - Emspak to John Knight Regarding Debt, September 24, 1940; 35.
    - Emspak to Joseph Slifko Regarding Press, September 24, 1940; 36.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, September 26-October 21, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Julius Emspak to Victor Larid Regarding Mailing List, September 26, 1940; 1.
    - Emspak to Conrad Grimes Regarding Mailing List, September 26, 1940; 2.
    - Emspak to Frank Motter Regarding Mailing List, September 26, 1940; 3.
    - Emspak to Marvin Miniard Regarding Mailing List, September 26, 1940; 4-5.
    - Emspak to Stephen Erdely Regarding Mailing List, September 26, 1940; 6.
    - Emspak to Neile Joseph Regarding Mailing List, October 10, 1940; 7.
    - Emspak to Miniard Regarding Mailing List, October 10, 1940; 8.
    - Emspak to Lilyan Salo Regarding Mailing List, October 10, 1940; 9.
    - Emspak to David Cunnigham Regarding Mailing List, October 10, 1940; 10.
    - Emspak to F. Zupancic Regarding Debt, October 14, 1940; 11.
    - Emspak to Fred Riemenschneider Regarding Mailing List, October 14, 1940; 12.
    - Emspak to Anthony Pirozzoli Regarding Debt, October 14, 1940; 13.
    - Emspak to Albert Horner Regarding Debt, October 14, 1940; 14.
    - Emspak to Charles Showalter Regarding Mailing List, October 14, 1940; 15.
    - Emspak to Motter Regarding Mailing List, October 14, 1940; 16.
    - Emspak to Harry Coates Regarding Mailing List, October 16, 1940; 17.
    - Emspak to Howard Angstadt Regarding Mailing List, October 16, 1940; 18.
    - Emspak to Aruthur Naugle Regarding Mailing List, October 16, 1940; 19.
    - Emspak to Salo Regarding Mailing List, October 16, 1940; 20.
    - Emspak to C.D. Lee Regarding Mailing List, October 17, 1940; 21.
    - Emspak to George Rothleitner Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 22.
    - Emspak to Charles Wollenhaupt Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 23.
    - Emspak to Motter Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 24.
    - Emspak to Miniard Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 25.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, October 18-December12, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Julius Emspak to Conrad Grimes Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 1.
    - Emspak to John Shailo Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 2.
    - Emspak to John Knight Regarding Mailing List, October 18, 1940; 3.
    - Emspak to Harry Harmon Regarding Mailing List, October 21, 1940; 4.
    - Emspak to Fred Riemenschneider Regarding Circular Letter, October 31, 1940; 5.
    - Emspak to Marvin Miniard Regarding Mailing List, November 8, 1940; 6.
    - Emspak to Frank Zupancic Regarding Statement, November 8, 1940; 7.
    - Emspak to Jacob Cambell Regarding Mailing List, November 8, 1940; 8.
    - Emspak to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Mailing List, November 13, 1940; 9.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Travel Order, November 15, 1940; 10.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding CIO Convention, December 2, 1940; 11.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Check, December 2, 1940; 12.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Bill, December 5, 1940; 13.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Convention, December 6, 1940; 14.
    - Emspak to Cambell Regarding Mailing List, December 19, 1940; 15.
    - Emspak to W. Nelson Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 16.
    - Emspak to Stephen Elderly Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 17.
    - Emspak to Miniard Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 18-19.
    - Emspak to Lilyan Salo Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 20.
    - Emspak to Harmon Regarding Mailing List, December 10, 1940; 21.
    - Emspak to Knight Regarding Mailing List, December 12, 1940; 22.
    - Emspak to Ada O'Donnell Regarding Mailing List, December 12, 1940; 23.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Petition, December 12, 1940; 24.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, December 18, 1940-September 5, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Julius Emspak to Lilyan Salo Regarding Mailing List, December 18, 1940; 1.
    - Emspak to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Hoover Plant, December 23, 1940; 2.
    - Emspak to Marvin Miniard Regarding Mailing List, December 26, 1940; 3.
    - Emspak to Conrad Grimes Regarding Mailing List, December 26, 1940; 4.
    - Emspak to Raymond Yeager Regarding Mailing List, December 26, 1940; 5.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Organizational Work, December 31, 1940; 6.
    - Emspak to George Rothleitner Regarding Mailing List, January 8, 1941; 7.
    - Emspak to Margaret Toth Regarding Mailing List, January 8, 1941; 8.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Address, January 14, 1941; 9.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Charter, January 22, 1941; 10.
    - Emspak to Alexander Adie Regarding Financial Report, March 4, 1941; 11.
    - Emspak to Adie Regarding Unemployment Insurance, April 10, 1941; 12.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Credentials, April 10, 1941; 13.
    - Emspak to Leo Kumle Regarding Union News, April 18, 1941; 14.
    - Emspak to Arthur Garfield Regarding Bonding, June 5, 1941; 15.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Barberton Situation, July 3, 1941; 16.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Union Transfer, July 11, 1941; 17.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Locals, July 16, 1941; 18.
    - Emspak to William Sentner Regarding Conversation with Umbreit, July 22, 1941; 19.
    - Emspak to Elizabeth Alexander Regarding Mailing List, August 4, 1941; 20.
    - Emspak to Toth Regarding Mailing List, August 4, 1941; 21.
    - Emspak to Richard Nieber Regarding Bill, August 8, 1941; 22.
    - Emspak to Harry Overstake Regarding Supplies, September 5, 1941; 23.
  - District 7 Incoming Correspondence, September 9, 1941-January 15, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Julius Emspak to Richard Gore Regarding Mailing List, September 9, 1941; 1.
    - Emspak to Joseph Vejlupek Regarding Mailing List, September 12, 1941; 2.
    - Emspak to Vejlupek Regarding Check, September 16, 1941; 3.
    - Emspak to H. Harmon Regarding Accounts, September 16, 1941; 4.
    - Emspak to Joseph Kress Regarding Press, October 4, 1941; 5.
    - Emspak to George Matthews Regarding Press, October 4, 1941; 6.
    - Emspak to Jacob Cambell Regarding Mailing List, October 10, 1941; 7.